Gilbert & Dil
Air Ni Cole Joy 2023 Hit Prayer!
Fujikyu Highland!
Yes, that's right.
K$ Vested Reward Location & Air Ni Cole Joy's Hit Prayer for 2023!
We went to Fujikyu Highland to pray for a hit in 2023.
This time, we came to Fujikyu Highland!
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy! I was so excited!
Do you guys have any private experience of visiting Fujikyu Highland for the first time?
Oh, yes!
So, is it your first time, too, Mayu?
Well, I'm from the countryside.
It's my first time here.
From the outside, you can see all the big roller coasters.
Fuji, and the view was great.
It's great. The fun is right in front of us.
It's going to be fun!
So, this time, I'm going to challenge you to pray for a hit.
I would like to announce the theme of what we are going to do at Fujikyu Highland!
Yes!
Here is the theme!
The theme is "Idol's challenge to get through even the scariest things with a smile!
Fuji & Shiver Maze with a smile!
Yes, that's right, this time
Fuji or the shivering labyrinth with a smile without running away!
By the way, I challenge you to pray for a hit this time.
The team that lost in the last challenge is the team of thieves.
The team on the right from the monocross?
Yes!
Yes, so, the team of "Light Thief" won!
What do you think? Should I come this far?
Well, we can do it.
I guess we can do it.
What's the matter? Anything?
Well, you know, if you have a favorite.
And Alice is a prize.
I'd like that.
What do you have in mind?
Okay, so the police team will have time to play together.
So, priority tickets, priority tickets to the attractions, and...
And some delicious sweets at the Yanbai.
Wow!
What do we do now?
Let's do it!
So, this time, Momo-san, you still have until tomorrow.
I've got this.
And then...
Until tomorrow, Momo-san.
Oh!
I'm so scared!
Well, I can't participate due to a leg injury, but I'm sure all the other members will be up for the challenge!
By the way, we will be divided into 4 for the Thousand Day Labyrinth and 7 for Fujiyama.
Let's see which team will challenge which attraction!
Okay, the Fujiyama team is Aida, Onishi, Murayama, Awano, Fujisawa, Yamano, and me!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Yay! Let's go for it!
Let's go for it! Let's have fun!
Okay, so the Sennichi Maze team is Ichihara, Emumi, Daihaku, and Takahashi!
Go! Go, go, go!
Well then, let's start with the Fujiyama team!
Let's go!
So, here we are at Fujiyama!
Yay!
The first four to ride are the four of us!
First four to ride, let's go!
Let's go for it!
Let's go!
The first one to go was smiling, and I think I can accomplish that.
Oh, oh!
With a smile, I'm going to be much, much more effective, and I'm going to do my best with a smile on my face!
Let's go for it! From whatever I want!
From whatever you want!
Let's get to it!
Yes, sir!Yes!
Yeah! Let's go!
Fast forward.
It's kind of cool that we're at the top of the mountain in Reno, and we're doing the original summit.
Yes, go, go, go, go, go!
I know I'm in the way, but....
Time is starting. I'm going to ride on Fujisan from now on!
I'm so glad to know that Aoi is totally fine with the race course for the first time!
Amazing!
Smile, quickly, idol's, idol's!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
They're here!
Here it comes!
That's so funny!
Well, I feel like I shouldn't be doing this, after seeing the reaction of the previous, uh, guests.
It's kind of stern!
But, their eyebrows were under their noses, so we were under our noses, too.
Pray for a hit! Pray for a hit!
Whoo!
Pray for a hit!
But it's silver, but it's white!
You're so lucky, coffee.
The coffee is so good!
I love it!
I think it's a New Jerkorro, Ute bar.
New Jarcolaw?
It's a little bit like New Jerky Craw with a little bit of a sheen on it.
I had ramen for lunch, and now I regret it.
I must have swallowed the soy sauce ramen, all of it.
Last supper.
My last supper was soy sauce ramen.
Departure!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Oh, no! Oh, man! Oh, man!
It feels so good.
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Smile! Smile!
I'm smiling! I'm smiling! He's smiling!
It's so slippery!
Stop!
Come on!
Hey!
Thank you!
Ever!
Guys!
Thank you!
Let's work hard so that March 2020 will be our debut!
Leah, please take care of me!
I will support you as hard as I can!
Riaji!
Riaji! Ria!
Ria!
Whoo-hoo!
Wah!
Teasing will not be tolerated!
Teasing doesn't bother me!
Aah!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
My hands are numb!
This is definitely a clue.
My hands are so dry,
My hair is in trouble.
My hands are numb!
Yuuki is tearing up.Yuuki is crying.
He's crying, crying.
Wow!
My hand!
Oh, my hand! My hands!
Time to go!
I'm ready!
Great!
Did I say something?
Just a hint.
Thank you!
That's great!
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous.
I'm not good at this.
If I ride the mini coaster for kids,
I won't be able to salute and go home.
I'll do my best,
I'll do my best, so you'll have to give me a hint.
I can't go home.
This is really bad. My blood pressure is really bad right now. It's really bad.
It's really bad. Why am I here now?
I'm a little scared when everyone says I'm scared.
I'm sure I'll be fine on the ride.
I'll do my best.
Wait a minute. Maybe I really can't.
I'm going home with a little breath
Hey, look, I cried.
I cried.
What's going on? Are you okay?
She's crying. Conor's crying.
Conor, are you okay?
I'm scared.
Is Conor okay?
Is he okay?
Oh, no!
I'm scared! I'm scared!
Come on, let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Come on!
Say something!
Awww!
It's okay!
I'm having fun!
What?
I'm smiling.
I'm smiling!
Oh, no!
It's not a smile!
Smile!
It's for the pit!
Pit stop!
This 10 meters!
In the last 10 meters!
Oh, no!
Oh no!
Chanting dive, approaching safety bar.
Oh, no!
It's the pit stop!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
Oh no!
Oh no! Oh no!
Get down a little bit.
No! No!
Yah! Yah!
Yah!Yah!
Ya!
Smile! Smile!
Aaaaah!
Oh no!
Interesting!
The mask moves so much!
It's not so much that it breaks, it's that the mask shifts.
The mask's bangs, mind you.
Oh, my God, the mask is so bad.
You're going to have a mental breakdown because of the mask.
What?
The mask is not strong enough?
I did my best!
It was fun.
I'm crying. I'm terrified.
Are you okay?
It started with tears in my eyes.
Thank you!
You did great!
Are you okay?
I was fine.
You did great.
Thanks, man.
You get some rest today.
Make sure you take a bath.
It's cold.
It's so cold, you're in three pieces.
He's talking!
Thank you for watching!
So, we are now on to the melody labyrinth!
These are the four who will challenge us in the melody labyrinth!
Good luck!
I'll do my best!
Are you okay? I've been worried about your color since a while ago.
It's really serious.
It's bad, isn't it, since you're a big kan?
That's right.
I'm going a little bit with just tears here.
But I thought, "With the four of us here, I'll be fine.
Yeah, I'm not alone.
Super, super, super.
Yeah, yeah.
Something like, you know, I thought it was Pappy Land, not Melody Maze.
That's right.
Kid's Kieland.
From Kidsquieland.
Smile.
OK!!!
There are only yuru-kyara.
There are only yuru-kyara to the fullest.
Yuru-kyara from Kids' Kiland.
I did my best!
Yes, so everyone go out and do your best!
I'm off!
I did my best!
I entrusted it to you!
I'll do my best!
What do you got?
I'll get a little something, and so will Tora.
Has it started already?
Answer me quickly!
What is it? Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Are you just taking pictures?
Why are you doing it again?Why are you doing it again?
Stop it, seriously.
I'm serious.
Aah!
I'm crying...
Why did you say "pooh-pooh"?
I'm not going to do anything, really.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
I'm tearing up.
(3) Explosion
Explosion
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
Sorry, guys!
Sorry for being so loud, guys!
I'm sorry I'm covering my ears!
I'm sorry, guys!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for being so loud!
Ow!
Can I have a laugh without making so much noise?
I'm sorry. Shut up, you!
Shut up, you!
I feel like Lennon's leading!
I love Lennon!
I love music!
Come to me, people.
Oh, that's not good enough?
Uh, don't you want to wear a mask?
I'm scared.
Maybe you should take a hit.
Let me see it. It's...
It's not over until we go.
I don't think so.
Excuse me.
I think she might have drunk the soba.
Why?
Don't take it, don't take it.
Are you sure you don't want me to take it?
Yeah, I'm sure.
My hand's out. I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Don't do it.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute. I got caught on an arrow.
Arrow.
You'll die.
I don't like it.
I really don't like it.
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
The bad part's over.
I'm getting really hungry.
Let's run.
I'm scared
Let's go.
[fast forward]
[fast forward] Come on!
It's okay. It's okay.Not funny, okay.
Elle's face, handsome.
Ha-ha-ha.
Scary.
Thank you. We're all in this together.
It's okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared. Oh, shit.
What is it?
It's okay, Viki. It's okay.
I'm scared.
Oh, shit.
I've seen this before.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm scared.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's coming so fast.
I'm so scared
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Here you go.
This way, this way.
I'm scared.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, Mr. Treyven.
He's waiting for you.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm gonna go now.
What's he like?
Wow.
Stop it!
You're scaring me.
Wow.
It's over.
I didn't know what to do.
Rena was leading the way.
She was really, really prepared and reliable.
But I was so scared.
From the very beginning.
I was scared to make it.
It's over now.
That was scary.
Welcome back, everyone.
Thank you, guys.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Michiaki.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you for trying.
Let's get a hit for sure!
We'll all do our best.
But, Lena, you're not breathing.
It was dark, but your face...
But I'm looking for something.
What? Did you get blown away?
I'm having so much fun.
But... Ayumi's okay, too.
How was it?How'd it go?
Genon led the way.
He did?
That was really reassuring.
Genon held Michitaro's light.
Oh, he held the light, too.
That was really great!
I was so happy.
Personally, I want to go.
I'm glad.
I breathed it in and I left.
And before, thank you for thinking of me.
How'd it go?
Thank you so much.
Wow.
Yes, so this is the hit period
Ujiyama and all of the established name families
And all of the established families
without anyone getting into a fight.
Hit period succeeded!
Yay!
You did a great job!
Thank you all for your hard work!
Yes, so today is the day.
I'd like to say that we got one thing over the hump.
Let this give you confidence.
I'm going to do my best with a lot of near-joy.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, actually, this is the reason why we are here.
Before taking the hit period, we all had a lot of fun in Ujiyama.
We had a lot of fun in Ujiyama
Please enjoy the vlog.
Please look forward to it!
Thank you very much.
Well, that's all for now.
That's all for now.
Bye bye!